A Guide to the Papers of the Proctor of the University of Virginia, (Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough), 1817-1828
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Dinsmore & Neilson 1827 April 23, ALS (copy). 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:716)
- Philip. Lightfoot to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 April 24, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:717)
- B[ernard] Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 April 25, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:718)
- B[ernard] Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 April 25, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:719)
- John Tayloe Lomax to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 April 25, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:720)
- W[illia]m Robinson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 April 29, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:721)
- Bernard Peyton to Brumnum & Wert 1827 May 1, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:722)
- George Tucker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 May 6, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:723)
- Joseph F. White to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 May 8, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:724)
- W[illia]m Wertenbaker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough - copies of 3 resolutions: 1827 May 12, ADS. 1 p. with addr; 1 p. with dkt; 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:725)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 May 14, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:726)
- Wait, Green & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough - notice of subscription renewal to Journal of Education1827 May 15, Pntd. 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:727)
- William A. Knox to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 May 21, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:728)
- John Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 May 29, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:729)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 May 31, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:730)
- Ja[me]s Marshall to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 June 1, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:731)
- C. Peyton to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 June 2, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:732)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 June 6, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:733)
- E[dward] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 June 6, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:734)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 June 7, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:735)
- John Tayloe Lomax to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 June 8, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 7:736)
- W[illia]m Wertenbaker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough - faculty resolution 1827 June 8, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 7:737)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 June 13, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:738)
- G[eorge] Tucker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 June 13, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:739)
- W[illia]m Wertenbaker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 June 15, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 7:740)
- John Tayloe Lomax to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 June 16, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:741)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 June 19, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:742)
- [James] Webster to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 June 19, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:743)
- Michael Anderson to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 June 20, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:744)
- D. J. Burr to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 June 23, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:745)
- V[alentine] W. Southall to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 July 9, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:746)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 July 11, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:747)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 July 14, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:748)
- John M. Perry to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 July 15, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:749)
- E. Grosthwait to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 July 17, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:750)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 July 19, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:751)
- Joseph F. White to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: bells 1827 July 19, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:752)
- Fortunatus Sydnor to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 July 28, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:753)
- Dinsmore & Neilson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 August 2, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:754)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 August 10, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:755)
- Sellers & Pennock to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: fire equipment 1827 August 11, ALS/Pntd. 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:756)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 August 16, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:757)
- Edwin C. Drummona to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 August 17, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:758)
- Benj[amin] Wright to General John H[artwell] Cocke 1827 August 18, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:759)
- James Madison to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Madison Papers] 1827 August 23, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:760)
- Ed. W. Sims to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 August 23, ALS, 1:00 PM. (Box-folder 7:761)
- Richard E. Parker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 August 31, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:762)
- W[illia]m Wertenbaker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 September 5, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:763)
- Sellers & Pennock to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 September 8, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:764)
- Nich[olas] P. Trist to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough - resolutions of the Board of Visitors, 1827 July 19 1827 September 11, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:765)
- John C. and Geo[rge] Newton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 September 12, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:766)
- Geo[rge] Hardaway to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 September 18, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:767)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 September 20, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:768)
- J[ohn]; P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough with draft, 1827 September 23, Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to J. P. Emmet 1827 September 20, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:769)
- C. & A. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 October 2, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:770)
- M. Grelter to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 October 6, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:771)
- W[illia]m Wertenbaker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: faculty resolution 1827 October 13, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:772)
- W[illia]m Mountjoy & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 October 20, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:773)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 October 22, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:774)
- W[illia]m Wertenbaker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: faculty resolution 1827 October 23, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:775)
- John Tayloe Lomax to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 October 27, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:776)
- James Madison to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Madison Papers] 1827 October 29, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:777)
- John Tayloe Lomax to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 October 31, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:778)
- Nich[olas] P. Trist to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] re: resolution 1827 November 2, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:779)
- Sarah Tayloe Nicolson to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 November 5, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:780)
- Th[omas] Boswell to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] [1827 November 9], ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:781)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: bell 1827 November 9, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:782)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 November 10, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:783)
- Philip. Lightfoot to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [1827 November 10], ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:784)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 November 15, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:785)
- John Taylor to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 November 16, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:786)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Tho[ma]s R. Harrison 1827 November 17, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:787)
- B[ernard] Peyton to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 November 17, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:788)
- C. & A. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 November 17, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:789)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 November 17, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:790)
- Dan[ie]l Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 November 17, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:791)
- W[illia]m Wertenbaker to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] - faculty resolution 1827 November 19, ADS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:792)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] re: bell 1827 November 22, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:793)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 November 23, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:794)
- Philip. Lightfoot to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 November 23, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:795)
- James Madison to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Madison Papers] 1827 November 24, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:796)
- Rich[ar]d E. Walker to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 November 24, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:797)
- Benj[amin] Blackford to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, receipt on verso signed John Wilks 1827 November 30, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:798)
- James Madison to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Madison Papers] 1827 December 2, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:799)
- W[illia]m Bolling to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 December 4, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:800)
- Edward C. Carrington to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 December 9, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:801)
- [P.] Ambler to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 December 10, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:802)
- W[illia]m M. Murphy to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 December 26, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:803)
- John S. May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 December 29, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:804)
- Van Lew, Baker & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 December 30, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:805)
- [Charles] Bonnycastle - plan for a fountain with sketch; proposal for instrument maker 1827, ADS. 2 p. with dockets (Box-folder 7:806)
- List of journals for Medical Department 1827, AD, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:807)
- W[illia]m Robinson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:808)
- Nich[olas] P. Trist to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: bell [1827], ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:809)
- N[icholas] P. Trist to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with enclosure of questions, 1 p. (draft of answers on verso) [1827], ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:810)
- Miscellaneous receipts 1827, ANS. 131 items. (Box-folder 7:811)
- G[eorge] Tucker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 January 17, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:812)
- Coleman Sellers to Gen. John [Hartwell] Cocke, includes sketch of brass valve 1828 January 19, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:813)
- Dan[ie]l Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 February 5, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:814)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with encl., 1828 February 12, W[illiam] Dandridge to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, 1 p 1828 February 18, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:815)
- W[illia]m Wertenbaker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 April 1, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:816)
- Edward C. Carrington to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 June 15, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:817)
- James Madison to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] [original in Madison Papers] 1828 June 21, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:818)
- R. H. Hobson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 June 27, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:819)
- William C. Mulligan to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 July 3, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:820)
- W[illia]m M. Murphy to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 July 10, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:821)
- Th[omas] Johnson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 July 16, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:822)
- Ja[me]s Dinsmore to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 July 22, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:823)
- George Tucker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with inserted note, signed "G.T.," 1 p 1828 July 25, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:824)
- James Madison to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Madison Papers] 1828 July 31, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:825)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 August 6, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:826)
- R. M. Patterson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 August 6, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:827)
- J[ohn]; P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 August 9, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:828)
- Thomas S. McClelland to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1828 August 11, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:829)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 August 23, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:830)
- Hall & Fitzgerald to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 August 23, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:831)
- C. L. Mosby to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1828 August 26, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:832)
- R. M. Patterson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 September 1, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:833)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 September 3, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:834)
- John Pratt to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 September 6, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:835)
- John Wickham to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 September 6, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:836)
- John Yates to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 September 8, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:837)
- Alexander Somervail to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1828 September 9, ALS, 2:00 PM. (Box-folder 7:838)
- Rich[ar]d E. Parker to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1828 September 10, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:839)
- V[alentine] W. Southall to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 September 11, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:840)
- Alexander Somervail to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1828 September 12, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:841)
- W[illia]m W. Norvell to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 September 14, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:842)
- Philip. Lightfoot to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1828 September 16, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:843)
- Henry P. Daingerfield to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 September 17, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:844)
- John Pratt to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 September 17, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:845)
- Cha[rle]s B. Austin to Th[omas] Johnson 1828 September 20, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:846)
- Dan[ie]l Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 September 27, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:847)
- W[illia]m W. Norvell to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1828 October 2, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:848)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 October 5, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:849)
- John F. Tompkins to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 October 5, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:850)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to A.S.b. 1828 October 8, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:851)
- Daniel McMahan to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 October 20, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:852)
- J[ohn] Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 October 25, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:853)
- H[enry] P. Daingerfield to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [1828 October 27], ALS frag. 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:854)
- W[illia]m W. Norvell to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1828 October 30, ALS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:855)
- Philip. Woodson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 November 10, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:856)
- Robley Dunglison to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 November 15, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:857)
- G[eorge] Tucker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 November 15, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:858)
- R. H. Alexander to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 November 17, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:859)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 November 18, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:860)
- N[icholas] P. Trist to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1828 November 26, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:861)
- Philip. Lightfoot to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1828 November 27, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:862)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 November 29, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:863)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1828 December 1, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:864)
- Geo[rge] D. Crosthwait to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 December 2, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:865)
- Briscoe G. Baldwin to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 December 3, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:866)
- John Pratt to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 December 4, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:867)
- R. H. Alexander to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 December 5, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:868)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to [Bright B. Garth], with ALS, 1828 December 7, B.B.G. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough on verso 1828 December 6, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:869)
- William C. Mulligan to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 December 6, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:870)
- Daniel McMahan to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 December 7, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:871)
- Philip. Lightfoot to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1828 December 9, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:872)
- H. W. Latan頴o Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 December 11, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:873)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1828 December 13, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:874)
- Briscoe G. Baldwin to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 December 19, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:875)
- Geo[rge] W. Spotswood to "Chairman of the Faculty" 1828 December 21, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:876)
- B. Trueheart to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 December 25, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:877)
- Benj[ami]n Brand to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1828 December 26, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:878)
- John N. Rose to Alexander Garret[t]1828 December 29, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:879)
- Faculty resolutions 1828, ADS. 14 items. (Box-folder 7:880)
- Miscellaneous receipts 1828, ANS. 157 items. (Box-folder 7:881)
- Material re: hydraulic cement and fire hoses 1828, Pntd. 4 items. (Box-folder 7:882)
- Professor [Charles] Bonnycastle's plan for curing smoky chimneys, with enclosed diagram, 1 p 1828, AD, 3 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:883)
- Papers 1829-1832 (Box 8)
- Papers 1832-1833 (Box 9)
- Papers 1833-1835 (Box 10)
- Papers 1836-1838 (Box 11)
- Papers 1839-1841 (Box 12)
- Papers 1841 (Box 13)
- Papers 1841-1842 (Box 14)
- Papers 1843-1849 (Box 15)
- 1851-1891, no date (Box 16)
- Papers 18089-1916 (Box 17)
- Papers 1821-1895 (Box 18)
- Papers 1827-1931 (Box 19)
- Papers 1838-1931 (Box 21)
- Papers 1887-1911 (Box 22)
- Papers 1883-1910 (Box 22)